不只是在我面前
And not just in front of me--
而是在所有工作人员面前
in front of the whole crew.
本字幕首发于字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
■
伊莱  我想说清楚
Eli, I want to be clear here.
翻译  杨爱菜       ABCpril翻译  丶Charl    鱼小姐啦
他们在一堆拿着
They were touching
摄像机的陌生人面前触摸对方
in front of strangers with cameras.
好  我去调查一下
Okay, let me look into it.
翻译  PiPi   MikeJiang  翻译  静妹粒    charcie
我们都知道
Now, we both know
彼得的竞选可经不起
Peter's campaign wouldn't withstand
这类闪失
the fallout of something like this.
艾丽西娅的洗白之路也无疑
And Alicia's rehabilitation would certainly
翻译  痒痒的小跟班校对  某羽
会因此事变成白费工夫
become a wasted effort.
我来处理
Okay, let me handle it.
-伊莱  你都不知道  -我说了我来处理
- Oh, Eli, you didn't even know! - I said I'd handle it!
时间轴  chance-coco时间轴  风吹来的那片云
后期   鱼骨头总监   夕橙橙
该死
Oh, damn.